<application>
  <component name="AppStorage">
    <histories>
      <item value="FETCH" />
      <item value="OFFSET" />
      <item value="Returns a view of the portion of this list between the specified fromIndex, inclusive, and toIndex, exclusive. (If fromIndex and toIndex are equal, the returned list is empty.) The returned list is backed by this list, so non-structural changes in the returned list are reflected in this list, and vice-versa. The returned list supports all of the optional list operations supported by this list. This method eliminates the need for explicit range operations (of the sort that commonly exist for arrays). Any operation that expects a list can be used as a range operation by passing a subList view instead of a whole list. For example, the following idiom removes a range of elements from a list: list.subList(from, to).clear(); Similar idioms may be constructed for indexOf and lastIndexOf, and all of the algorithms in the Collections class can be applied to a subList. The semantics of the list returned by this method become undefined if the backing list (i.e., this list) is structurally modified in any way other than via the returned list. (Structural modifications are those that change the size of this list, or otherwise perturb it in such a fashion that iterations in progress may yield incorrect results.) Params: fromIndex – low endpoint (inclusive) of the subList toIndex – high endpoint (exclusive) of the subList Returns: a view of the specified range within this list" />
      <item value="Returns true if the specified object is equal to this enum constant. Params: other – the object to be compared for equality with this object. Returns: true if the specified object is equal to this enum constant." />
      <item value="Serial Number" />
      <item value="IDENTITY INSERT" />
      <item value="criteria" />
      <item value="placeholder" />
      <item value="Invoice Process" />
      <item value="DBAppender cannot function if the JDBC driver does not support getGeneratedKeys method and without a specific SQL dialect" />
      <item value="violations" />
      <item value="release Config Service" />
    </histories>
    <option name="languageScores">
      <map>
        <entry key="CHINESE" value="11" />
        <entry key="ENGLISH" value="12" />
      </map>
    </option>
  </component>
  <component name="Cache">
    <option name="lastTrimTime" value="1635755635057" />
  </component>
</application>